amritatv.com 2016-05-19

# Welcome to Amrita TV

|  |   |  | PRIVACY POLICY   
---  

Your privacy on the Internet is important to us, which is why we at AmritaTV believe in an active approach to safeguarding your privacy online. You can interact and remain assured that you are protected by confidentiality, security, and your individual right to change your mind.   

Confidentiality   
Any personally identifiable information you do provide us will not be shared, sold, swapped or marketed to any third parties .The exception may be the names of the winners for any promotions or any prize draws we ran as would be outlined in the terms and conditions of that promotion .The information you do provide us with may be used in the following ways, unless stated otherwise. 

1) to help us better understand the demographics and needs of our market.  
2) To improve the quality of our services.  
3) To obtain feedback on how we can improve our site.  
4) For contacting winners of promotions or prize draws.  
5) To inform you about additional services.  
6) amritatv.com will not disclose your personal information ,without notice, only if required to do so by law or on the good (faith) a) that such action is necessary to comply with any legal process b)protect and defend the rights or property of amritatv.com c)to protect the personal safety of users of amritatv.com, its websites or the public.  

Log Files   
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use this information only to determine how to make future visits more convenient and productive.   
   
Children  
We do not intend to collect personal information from anyone under the age of 14. If you are under 14, you should not enter information on this web site and should ask a parent to do so for you.  
   
Subscriptions  
You will receive e-mails or mailings from amritatv.com only if you request to be included in our correspondence list. If you are currently on our list and do not wish to receive further information from us, simply tell us by following the unsubscribe instruction contained in any e-mail we send.  
   
Cookies  
Cookies are a feature of Web browser software. A cookie is a piece of data that is sent to a Web site visitor's web browser and placed on the hard drive of the visitor's computer to identify their computer to the web site. Most web browsers are automatically set up to receive cookies. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or, if you wish to be notified when a cookie is being sent, you can do so by indicating or by revising your browser preferences.  
   
Links   
Although our site may contain links to other sites, we are not responsible for content, links, or privacy on any of those sites.  
   
Your Comments and Suggestions   
We always appreciate hearing from you and welcome your comments and e-mails. But we advise you that you exercise good judgment, because material we receive will be considered public and non-confidential. Additionally, we reserve the right to use any comments and e-mails you share without limitation.  
   
Questions   
If you have further questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of our site, or your experience with our site, you may contact us at  [webmaster@amritatv.com](mailinto:webmaster@amritatv.com)  
   
Legal  
By visiting this site you are agreeing to the terms as outlined above and in the Credits and Copyrights section. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time.   

Leave a Comment  
Disclaimer - Posting comments that are abusive, vulgar, personal or incendiary is subject to legal action. Irrelevant comments and hyperlinks cannot be published.  

Write a comment ...

Post comment

Cancel
